Kentucky Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty; Records apap401
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- KCADP Corporate Documents, 1965-2022
  - Grants
    - Current Annual Operating Budget and Actual, 2009 January 1-2009 July 31
    - KCADP Current Annual Operating Budget and Actual, 2010 January 1-2010 July 31
    - KCADP Final Report Grant #TFR13-02565, 2013-2014
    - KCADP Bank Balance For Grant, 2020 January 1-2020 August 13
  - KCADP Bylaws
    - KCADP Bylaws, 1988-2000 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Corporate Documents, 2008-2013 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Original Bylaws, 1988 June 28
    - KCADP Articles of Incorporation, 1988 December 15
    - Amended Bylaws, 1991 May 14
    - 501c3 IRS Document, 2008 August 11
    - Bylaws with Comments About Possible Changes, 2008 August 31
    - Bylaws, 2008 August 31
    - KCADP New Bylaw Provisions, Draft 1, 2012 September 1
    - KCADP New Bylaw Provisions, Draft 2, 2012 September 10
    - Bylaws Questions For Jeff, 2012 October 13
    - KCADP New Bylaw Provisions, Draft 3, 2012 November 24
    - Final Bylaws Adopted by the Board, 2013 March
    - National Death Penalty Proposal, 2013
    - Amended Bylaws, 2013 March 11
    - KCADP New Bylaw Provisions, Draft 4, 2013 March 11
    - KY Tax Exempt Certificate for Dell, 2015 June 21
    - Amended Bylaws, 2018 March 12
    - Bylaws with Text of Proposed Amendments, 2016
    - State Tax Exempt Document, 1965-2022
    - KY Tax Exempt Certificate Template, 1965-2022
  - KCADP Employee Records
    - Staff Annual Work Plan Template, 2016 January 4
    - "Some thoughts about organizing", 2021 March 29
    - Six Month Summary, 2021 September 1
    - September Measurables #1: T. Lumpkin, 2021 September 1
    - September Measurables #2: T. Lumpkin, 2021 September 1
    - Letter from Doug Stern to Governor Patton, 2003 June 19
    - Director of Public Education & Outreach Job Posting, with notes, 2005 August 9
    - Notes from meeting with Ruslyn Case-Compton and Nancy Jo Kemper, 2006 May 10
    - Notes from meeting with Sr. Dorothy Schuette, 2006 May 25
    - Letter from Doug Stern to Ms. Malvina Sheffield, 2006 June 12
    - Sampleletter to Rep. Joe Fischer or Sen. Katie Stine, 2006 June 12
    - Faith-group Legislative Initiative Progress Report Number 4, 2006 July 31
    - Doug Stern Contacts, 2007 June 2
    - KCADP Fact Sheet, 2007 June 8
    - Copy for PowerPoint presentation, 2007 July 12
    - Letter from Doug Stern to Lee Thomas Jr., 2007 July 24
    - KCADP Presentation- New PowerPoint Format, 2007 August 13
    - KCADP Final Presentation, 2007 August 13
    - Faith-group Legislative Initiative Progress Report Number 6, 2007 September 30
    - Doug Stern Invoice for Faith-Group Legislative Initiative, 2007 October 1
    - Don Vish Photograph, 2007 October 19
    - Director of Public Education & Outreach Job Posting Original, 2008 September 3
    - Director of Public Education & Outreach Job Posting Final, with notes, 2008 September 9
    - Personnel Policy of KCADP, 2008 September 10
    - Don Vish Cover Letter, 2008 October 14
    - KCADP Classified Advertisement 2nd Draft with Carl, 2008 October 28
    - KCADP Classified Advertisement Final, 2008 October 29
    - Lisa K. Work Cover Letter for Director of Public Education Position, 2008 November 3
    - Erin Herbert Cover Letter for Director of Public Education, 2008 November 3
    - Rachel M. Hurst Cover Letter for Director of Public Education, 2008 November 8
    - Linda D. Bullock Cover Letter for Director of Public Education, 2008 November 9
    - Michael Jennings Cover Letter for Director of Public Education, 2008 November 18
    - Java Ahmed Cover Letter for Director of Public Education, 2008 November 19
    - (The Rev. Dr.) Donna T. Morton Cover Letter for Director of Public Education, 2008 November 25
    - Karen C. Jones Cover Letter for Director of Public Education, 2008 November 25
    - Patricia Jackson Blue Cover Letter for Director of Public Education Position, 2008 November 28
    - Patricia Jackson Blue Cover Letter for Director of Public Education Position, 2008 November 28
    - List of Applicants Seeking the KCADP Position, 2008 December 1
    - Don Vish Work Agreement- With Edits, 2008 December 20
    - Don Vish Work Agreement- Draft, 2008 December 20
    - Don Vish Work Agreement-Final, 2008 December 20
    - KCADP Conference/Meeting/Travel Expense Report, 2008 December 29
    - KCADP Mileage/Meal Expense Report, 2008 December 29
    - Job Posting-Death Penalty Field Organizer for Southern California, 2009 November 30
    - KFTC Salary Information, 2013 January 16
    - KCADP Staff Evaluation, 2015 December 26
    - "Free Lexington's heart of monuments to traitorous slaveholders; it's really not that complicated" Op-Ed By Russell Allen, 2017 March 27
    - KCADP Director of Organzing Job Listing, 2021 January 23
    - Russell Allen Resume, 2021 January 25
    - Russell Allen - Cover Letter, 2021 January 25
    - Tialisha Lumpkin Cover Letter, 2021 April 25
    - Tialisha Lumpkin Resume, 2021 April 25
    - KCADP Organizing Goals, 2021 June 11
    - Measurables Report: T. Lumpkin, 2021 August 1
    - Measurables Report: T. Lumpkin, 2021 August 26
    - Measurables Report: T. Lumpkin, 2021 September 10
    - Facebook Cover Photo, 2021 December 13
    - Sample Presentation to Coalition Partners, 2009 July
    - KFTC Community Organizing Positions-Round 1 Interview Questions, 2012
    - KFTC Community Organizing Positions-Round 2 Interview Questions, 2012
    - KCADP Statewide Community Organizer Job Description, 2013
    - KCADP Statewide Community Organizer Job Description- Draft, 2013
    - SL Time Sheet Summary Oct - Dec, 2014
    - Shekinah Work Plan, 2014
    - ACLU Time Sheet Template, 2014
    - Excerpt from: Tialisha Lumpkin "Felon Disenfranchisement", 2016
    - Excerpt from: Tialisha "A Perspective and Call to Action", 2020
    - Don Vish- Report from Attendance of NCADP Convention, 2011 January 14-2011 January 16
    - Don Vish- Outreach, Education & Advocacy Report, 2011 March 14-2011 March 31
    - Don Vish- Outreach, Education & Advocacy Report, 2011 April 1-2011 April 14
    - Don Vish- Outreach, Education & Advocacy Report, 2011 April 29-2011 May 14
    - Don Vish- Outreach, Education & Advocacy Report, 2011 June 15-2011 June 28
    - Don Vish- Outreach, Education & Advocacy Report, 2011 July 29-2011 August 28
    - Don Vish- Outreach, Education & Advocacy Report, 2011 August 29-2011 September 14
    - Co-Director Update- Russell Allen, With Questions, 2021 July 26-2021 July 30
    - Co-Director Update- Russell Allen, 2021 July 26-2021 July 30
    - Co-Director Update- Russell Allen, 2021 August 2-2021 August 13
    - Co-Director Update- Russell Allen, With Questions, 2021 August 2-2021 August 13
    - Co-Director Update- Russell Allen, 2021 August 30-2021 September 10
    - Co-Director Update- Russell Allen, 2021 September 13-2021 September 24
    - Co-Director Update- Tialisha Lumpkin, 2021 October 1-2021 October 13
    - Co-Director Update- Russell Allen, 2021 October 11-2021 October 22
    - Co-Director Update- Tialisha Lumpkin, 2021 October 14-2021 October 28
    - Co-Director Update- Russell Allen, 2021 October 25-2021 November 5
    - Co-Director Update- Tialisha Lumpkin, 2021 October 29-2021 November 13
  - Executive Board Documents
    This subseries is arranged into two subsubseries.
    - Board Meeting Minutes and Agendas, 1989-2021
      - Executive Board Meeting Minutes and Subcommittees Minutes, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 12)
      - Executive Board Meeting Minutes and Subcommittees Minutes, 1990-2001 (Box 1, Folder 13)
      - Executive Meeting Agendas, 1992-2001 (Box 1, Folder 14)
      - Board Member Information, 2001 March 31
      - Board Meeting Notes, 2002 March 21
      - Board Meeting Minutes, 2002 September 24
      - Board Meeting Minutes, 2004 September 20
      - Board Meeting Minutes, 2005 May 24
      - Email Coordinating Book Events Via the Board, 2005 July 31
      - Board Pledges to Date for 3 Year Plan, 2008 January 28
      - Board Meeting Minutes, 2009 December 8
      - Board Meeting Minutes, 2011 June 13
      - Board Meeting Minutes, 2012 June 9
      - Board Meeting Minutes, 2012 September 12
      - Board Meeting Minutes, 2012 December 10
      - Board Meeting Minutes, 2013 March 11
      - Board Meeting Minutes, 2013 June 10
      - Board Meeting Minutes, 2014 March 10
      - Board Meeting Minutes, 2014 June 9
      - Board Meeting Minutes, 2014 September 8
      - Board Meeting Agenda, 2014 December 8
      - Bopard Meeting Minutes, 2014 December 8
      - Board Meeting Minutes, 2015 March 9
      - Board Meeting Agenda, 2015 June 8
      - Board Meeting Minutes, Amended, 2015 June 8
      - Board Meeting Minutes, 2015 September 14
      - Board Meeting Minutes, 2015 September 14
      - Board Meeting Agenda, 2015 September 14
      - Board Meeting Minutes, 2016 June 13
      - Board Meeting Minutes, 2016 September 12
      - Randy Steidl Final Report Fall 2016, 2016 November 29
      - Board Meeting Minutes, 2016 December 12
      - Board Meeting Minutes, 2017 March 13
      - Quarter 1 Transactions, 2017 June 11
      - Board Meeting Agenda, 2017 June 12
      - Board Meeting Agenda, 2017 September 11
      - Board Meeting Agenda, 2017 December 11
      - Board Meeting Minutes, 2018 March 12
      - Board Meeting Agenda, 2018 June 11
      - Board Meeting Minutes, 2018 June 11
      - Board Meeting Minutes, 2018 September 10
      - Board Meeting Agenda, with edits, 2018 December 10
      - Board Meeting Minutes, 2019 March 11
      - Board Meeting Minutes, draft with Pat edits, 2019 June 10
      - Board Meeting Minutes, 2019 September 9
      - Board Meeting Minutes, 2019 September 19
      - Board Meeting Minutes, 2020 June 8
      - Board Meeting Minutes, 2020 September 14
      - Board Meeting Agenda, 2020 September 14
      - KCADP River City Bank Statements, 2020 September 30
      - Board Meeting Agenda, 2020 December 12
      - Board Meeting Minutes, 2021 March 8
      - Board Meeting Minutes, 2021 June 14
      - Board Meeting Agenda, 2021 September 13
      - Budget for Three-Year, Full-Time KCADP Staffer, 2008
      - KCADP River City Checking Bank Statements, Quarter 3, 2021
      - KCADP Transactions, 2014 January 1-2014 December 31
      - KCADP Financial Statements for Fiscal Year 2013, 2013-2014
      - KCADP Net Worth- Balance Sheet Report, 2014 January 1-2014 December 31
      - KCADP Sister Helen Event Report, 2014 January 1-2014 December 31
      - 3rd Quarter Balance Sheet Reports, 2014 July 1-2014 September 30
      - 3rd Quarter Income& Expense Reports, 2014 July 1-2014 September 30
      - KCADP Income & Expense Report, 2014 July 1-2014 December 31
      - Transactions Month-By-Month, 2016 January 1-2016 June 30
      - 3rd Quarter Treasurer Report, 2016 July 1-2016 September 30
      - Fall Transactions, 2017 September-2017 November
      - KCADP River City Bank Statements, 2017 September 29-2017 November 30
      - KCADP River City Bank Statements, 2017 December 29-2018 February 28
      - KCADP Financial Report with Income and Expenditures, 2019 March-2019 May
    - Board Outreach to Supporters, 2016
      - Script for Board Outreach, Draft, 2016-01-26
      - Script for Board Outreach, Draft with AJB edits, 2016-02-01
      - Senator Westerfield Constituents in VV Database, 2016-02-03
  - Fundraising
    This subseries contains one subsubseries.
    - Fundraising, 1981-1993 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Letter to Dede Stokes, 2003 August 15
    - Letter to Ollie and Nancy Barber, 2003 August 15
    - Louisville Membership Dues List, 2003 October 9
    - KCADP Appeal Letter for Fundraising, 2003 November 14
    - Letter for Fundraising- Template, 2005 May 9
    - Letter about "The Biblical Truth about America's Death Penalty" by Dale S. Recinella Book and Visit, 2005 August 15
    - Photograph of Sister Helen Prejean, 2006 November 22
    - Sister Helen Prejean Reception Invitation, 2006 December 20
    - Plans and Notes for "Seize the New Day" Fundraising Campaign, 2011 June 9
    - Next Step Campaign Achievements Text, 2011 October 25
    - Britt and Paula Brockman Fundraiser and Reception Invitation, 2012 October 3
    - Letter to Rt. Rev. Damien Thompson from Father Paul Delahanty, 2003 August 15
    - Proteus Fund Partnering Letter, 2012 November 16
    - What is Lobbying Under the 501(h) Election?, 2013 May 14
    - KCADP Master List of Donors Over $100, 2014 April 30
    - KCADP Letter from Ben Griffith and Ruth Lowe from Murder Victims' Family Members for Reconciliation, 2014 August
    - Donor History for Donations over $100, 2014-2016
    - Letter from Rev. Patrick Delahanty RE: Nebraska Successful Abolition, 2015 May 28
    - Press Release: Victims' Family Members Issue Challenge Grant to Support Repeal, 2015 September 17
    - Individual "Impact" Donations, 2015-2016
    - W-9 For ForImpact Inc., 2016 January 1
    - KCADP Client Discovery – Tides Cohort, Draft, 2016 September 22
    - KCADP Client Discovery – Tides Cohort, Final, 2016 September 22
    - Notes from Coaching Four Prospects, 2017 January 3
    - Letter to Abbot Damien at Abbey of Gethsemani, 2005 August
    - KCADP Spring Fundraising Letter, 2014 April
    - Postage Report for Mailing of KCADP Spring Fundraising Letter, 2014 April
    - KCADP Invities You to Double Your Gift, 2014 October
    - KCADP Fundraising Letter from Michael VonAllmen, Previous Death Row Inmate, 2014 October
    - Letter: Victims' Family Members Issue Challenge Grant to Support Repeal, 2015 September
    - KCADP Fundraising Letter from Michael VonAllmen, Previous Death Row Inmate, 2015 November
    - Farley Printing List for Mailing, 2015 November
    - Mike VonAllmen and Kirk Bloodsworth Photograph, 2015 November
    - Anonymous Donation Image with Envelope, Color, 2016 April
    - Letter from Rev. Patrick Delahanty RE: Fundrasing Allocation, 2016 May
    - Mailing List, 2016 May
    - KCADP Letter Requesting Support from Tulio Tourinho, 2016 September
    - Donations from "Full Court Press", 2016 October
    - KCADP Getting Started with The Suddes Group Document, 2016 October
    - List of Fundraising Prospects, with notes, 2016 November
    - List of Fundraising Prospects, 2016 November
    - Draft of Predisposition Letter, 2016 November
    - KCADP Fundraising Letter, 2017 May
    - KCADP Fundraising Letter, 2017 November
    - Letter to Dede Stokes, 2006
    - Fundraising Thank You Letter from KCADP, 2012
    - More Money for More Good Fundraising Tips, 2012
    - Fundraising Thank You Letter from KCADP, 2013
    - Blue Toolkit- Supporting Document, 2014
    - KCADP Spring Fundraising Envelope for Mailing, 2014
    - Report to Accompany KCADP Spring Fundraising Letter, 2014
    - Fundraising Letter from Rev. Patrick Delahanty, 2015
    - Tides Foundation Death Penalty Abolition Capacity Building Grants Request for Proposal, 2016
    - Engagement Tool, Created by KCADP, Draft, 2017
    - Engagement Tool Edits by ForImpact, Draft, 2019
    - KCADP Access Data for all Donations, 1965-2022
    - Physical Mailing Master Files, 1965-2022
    - Fundraising for Carl Donations List, 2001 April 1-2002 September 30
    - Fund Request from JEHT, 2004 January 1-2004 December 31
    - PayPal Donation Report, 2014 January 1-2014 August 26
    - Donations from PayPal Transaction History, 2014 January 1-2014 November 29
    - Donations from Members, 2014 March 13-2014 November 26
    - KCADP Checking Account Balance, 2016 January 30-2016 June 30
    - Invoice #1324 from ForImpact for Coaching Program, 2016 October 7-2016 November 30
  - Treasurer's Reports
    - Treasurer's Reports-Louisville Chapter, 1989-1993 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Treasurer's Reports-State Level, 1989-1993 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Death Penalty and the Catholic Church, 1989-2015
  This series contains materials involving the Catholic church's efforts to support the abolition of the death penalty through the Kentucky Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (KCADP); including: training to equip church leaders for advocacy, the evangelical call to civic responsibility, the Ministry Against Death Penalty, and the Kentucky Council of Churches.
  This series contains four subseries.
  - Activities, 1990-2016
    - Sisters of Mercy Endorsement, 1990; 2000 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Faith and Justice: Exploring the Crisis of Empathy Conference, 2016 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Ecumencial Prayer Service for Reconciliation and Compassion at the Time of an Execution", 2004 November 15
    - Resolution Calling for Abolition of the Death Penalty, from the Archdiocese of Louisville Priests' Council, 2000 August
    - Knights of Colombus Resolution Supporting the Kentucky Catholic Bishops' Position on the Death Penalty, 2001 August
    - Project Budget for Dead Man Walking School Theatre Project, 2012 October 15-2013 October 14
    - Catholic Mobilizing Network Save the Date, 2013 April 16-2013 April 17
  - Communications, 2002-2014
    - Raleigh, North Carolina Presentation, 2002 September 21
    - Christians and Capital Punishment "A Report of the Christian Life Comission of the Baptist General Convention of Texas", 2003 January 10
    - Raleigh, North Carolina Presentation Mofidifed for Bowling Green, Kentucky, 2003 January 26
    - Letter from Pat Delahanty Inviting Members to "Live Man Talking: Juan Melendez; On Surviving Death Row"in Louisville, 2003 April 8
    - KCADP and Floridians for Alternatives to the Death Penalty Invitation to "Live Man Talking: Juan Melendez; On Surviving Death Row"in Louisville, 2003 April 18
    - Letter to New York Times and National Catholic Reporter Regarding Departure of Frank Keating, 2003 June 22
    - Catholic Conference of Kentucky Letter to Attorney General Regarding Mr. Slaughter's Death Sentence, 2007 April 2
    - Catholic Conference of Kentucky Letter to Pastor/Administrator, 2007 September 5
    - Letter to Catholic Parishes from Pat Delahanty, KCADP, and Kaye Gallagher Next Big Step Campaign Director, 2008 August 29
    - "A Good Friday Reflection to End the Use of the Death Penalty" Brochure, 2012 March 3
    - "Diminishing All of Us: The Death Penalty in Louisiana", Brief, 2012 March 17
    - Provincial Letter from Catholic Mobilizing Network, Draft, 2014 April 4
    - National Catholic Reporter Article "The Coarseness of Our Times", 2014 May 2
    - TylorStandley.com Article "The Death Penalty: Killing the Work of Christ (A Response to Al Mohler)", 2014 May 2
    - "Jurisprudence that Necessarily Embodies Moral Judgment: The Eigth Amendment, Catholic Teaching, and Death Penalty Discourse", 2012
  - Doctrine, 1989-2000
    - Death Penalty and Catholic Doctrine (1/2), 1989-2000 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Death Penalty and Catholic Doctrine (2/2), 1989-2000 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Training Documents, 2011-2016
    - Pastoral Leading Training Ad Number 2, from KCADP and Kentuckians For the Commonwealth for Labor, 2011 July 12
    - Pastoral Leading Training Ad Number 1, from KCADP and Kentuckians For the Commonwealth for Labor, 2011 July 12
    - Registrants for Pastoral Leader Training, 2011 November 19
    - List of Churches in Pendelton County, 2013 July 1
    - Assembly of God Spreadhseet, 2016 April 2
    - "Diminishing All of Us: The Death Penalty in Louisiana," A study for Louisiana Catholics Committed to Repeal of the Death Penalty, Full, 2012
    - Exoneree Tour Churches List, 2013
  - Equipping Church Leaders for Advocacy
    - Further Equipping Church Leaders Who Oppose the Death Penalty in Kentucky, Draft, 2011 April 13
    - Email from Marian McClure Taylor to Pat Delahanty Regarding Summary of Equipping Project, Attached, 2011 May 2
    - Email from Marian McClure Taylor Regarding the Possibility of Berea Equipping Conference, 2011 May 4
    - The Record Newsletter, Vol. 133 No. 29, 2011 July 28
    - Berea Friends Meeting, Rental Agreement, 2011 September 3
    - Education for Justice, "Respect for Life: CST and the Death Penalty, 2011", 2011 September 26
    - Letter to Catholic Clergy from Pat Delahanty, 2011 October 12
    - Catholic Conference of Kentucky Letter Offering Clergy Education About the Death Penalty, 2011 October 13
    - Pastoral Equipping Event Planning Meeting, 2011 November 14
    - Training for Pastoral Leaders to End the Death Penalty in Kentucky, Registration List, 2011 November 20
    - Constant Contact List for Equipping Pastoral Leaders to Advocate for Abolition, 2011 November 20
    - Event Notes by Don Vish, 2011 December 20
    - Event Notes by Marian McClure, 2011 December 20
    - Letter to Govenor Brownback and Members of the Kansas Legislature, 2012 July 24
    - Death Penalty Information Center "What to Say Messaging from DPIC's Report, "Struck by Lightning," and Results from a Survey of 1500 Registered Voters Nationwide" Presentation, 2011 November
    - Life Matters: The Death Penalty Brochure, 2011
    - Schedule for Equipping Pastoral Leaders to Advocate for Abolition Event, 2011 November 16-2011 November 17
    - Kentucky Council of Churches, Draft Executive Board Roster, 2013-2014
    - Text for Yahoo Group Invitation for Equipping Pastoral Leaders to Advocate for Abolition Event, Unknown
  - Evangelical Call to Civic Responsibility
    - "For the Health of the Nation: An Evangelical Call to Civic Responsibility" Document, 2004
  - Kentucky Council for Churches
    - The Kentucky Council of Churches Banner, Graphic, 2011 June 30
    - Kentucky Council of Churches, Executive Board Roster, 2012-2012
  - Ministry Against Death Penalty
    - Ministry Against the Death Penalty Board Meeting, Conference Call, 2012 May 9
    - Ministry Against the Death Penalty, Comments on Financial Report, 2012 June 30
    - Dead Man Walking School Theatre Project Report, 2012 July 27
    - Ministry Against the Death Penalty, Ohio Report, 2012 August 3
    - Ministry Against the Death Penalty Board Meeting, Conference Call Minutes, 2012 August 3
    - Ministry Against the Death Penalty, Comments on Financial Report, 2012 September 30
    - Dead Man Walking School Theatre Project Report, MADP Board Report, 2012 November 9
    - Draft of America Harvest Article for America Magazine, 2012 November 14
    - Ministry Against the Death Penalty Meeting Minutes, 2013 January 3
    - Catholic Mobilizing Network "Capital Punishment: Who Is it Serving" Presentation, 2013 February 2
    - Letter to Helen and Susanne from Ed Regarding Strategy for Establishing the First Part-Time Position of Special Project Manager, 2013 February 4
    - Meeting with Ministry Against the Death Penalty and DePaul University, 2013 February 6
    - MADP Executive Committee Meeting Minutes, Phone Conference, 2013 February 6
    - Transition Document for Play Project, 2013 February 11
    - Memo to MADP Board Members Regarding Update, 2013 February 15
    - Ministry Against the Death Penalty, Comments on 2013 Financial Report, 2013 March 31
    - Dead Man Walking School Theatre Project, Interim Report to Fetzer Institute, 2013 April 15
    - List of Ways RLC and MC Can Engage Against the Death Penalty for Maryland, 2013 April 22
    - Dead Man Walking School Theatre Project, MADP Board Report, 2013 April 30
    - Ministry Against the Death Penalty Update, 2013 May 1
    - Ministry Against the Death Penalty, Helen's Report, 2013 May 3
    - Ministry Against the Death Penalty, Board Agenda, 2013 May 3
    - Ministry Against the Death Penalty Meeting Minutes, 2013 May 3
    - Preliminary Notes for Meeting with Random House Regarding Re-Issue of Dead Man Walking, 2013 May 3
    - Report from Kentucky Board Meeting, MADP, 2013 May 3
    - Patrick Delahanty Resignation Letter from Board Position at the Catholic Conference of Kentucky, 2013 May 14
    - Patrick Delahanty Resignation Letter to Sister Marianne Race, CSJ from Board Position, 2013 May 14